I could be totally over reacting and
over worried right now. That's what you
got to understand. And we could be
totally fine. Like I said, November
comes, we recover like we always do, and
none of this [__] matters. But, you
just cannot be surprised if the
short-term top actually did turn into a
long-term top, man. Cuz that that could
be crazy. That could wipe out so many
people's fortunes, lives. So many people
could be so [__]
if they didn't see this coming. And, you
know, when you have reason to see and
believe that, man, something of that
caliber magnitude could actually hit,
and you have sufficient reasons and and
tendencies in the charts that are there
to support that actually being
a real possibility,
man, it would suck for you to be on the
complete wrong side or not even be
thinking about it.